<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MakeDecision</string>
    <string name="add_decision">Add decision</string>
    <string name="about_us">Info</string>
    <string name="add_description">Add description</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="clear_decisions">Delete decision</string>
    <string name="clear_description">Delete description</string>
    <string name="delete_all">Delete all</string>
    <string name="delete_all_decisions">Are you sure you want to delete all decisions?</string>
    <string name="delete_all_descriptions">Delete all descriptions?</string>
    <string name="delete_description">Delete this decision?</string>
    <string name="delete_single_description">Delete this description?</string>
    <string name="description_rait">Raiting</string>
    <string name="description_was_added">Description added! You can add another one in this square or fill another square! Also you can calculate your decision clicked on chart icon!</string>
    <string name="edit_description">Update description</string>
    <string name="edit_hint_description">Edit description then click \"+\"</string>
    <string name="enter_description">Add description and severity\n then click \"+\"</string>
    <string name="enter_question">Please enter the name of decision!</string>
    <string name="get_my_decisions">My decisions</string>
    <string name="make_decision">Make decision</string>
    <string name="please_enter_description">Please enter description and set severity (from 1 to 5), then click \"+\"</string>
    <string name="txtv_enter_question">Please enter the question:</string>
    <string name="what_will_if_it_doesnt_happen">What will be if it <b><i>DOESN\'T</i></b> happen?</string>
    <string name="what_will_if_it_happens">What will be if it happens?</string>
    <string name="what_wont_be_if_id_doesnt_happens">What <b><i>WON\'T</i></b> be if it <b><i>DOESN\'T</i></b> happen?</string>
    <string name="what_wont_be_if_it_happens">What <b><i>WON\'T</i></b> be if it happens?</string>
    <string name="hint_enter_the_question">Enter the question\n or a name of problem\n then click \"+\"</string>
    <string name="calculate">Calculate</string>
    <string name="edit_decision_name">Edit</string>
    <string name="delete_one">Delete</string>
    <string name="decart_title">About technique\n“Descartes Square”</string>
    <string name="descarts_sqare_technique"><p>This technique “Descartes Square” allows to consider a question from four sides. You need to answer four questions for this:\n\n1)\tWhat will happen if it takes place?\n2)\tWhat will happen if it doesn’t take place?\n3)\tWhat will not happen if it takes place?\n4)\tWhat will not happen if it doesn’t take place?\n\nIn this way you will work up the solution to the question in all possible options.\n\nHow to use\n\nFirst, choose point “Make a decision”. Then type question that you are interested in and press “+”. You will see square with four questions and a diagram. You can choose any question and start answering. Each answer has to be evaluated (how important it is for you) from 1 to 5; after you do it press “+”. The more answers you give the easier it will be to make a decision. After all or few squares will be filled in, you can press the diagram icon. You will see a diagrammatical result with more and less suitable options in percentage.\nLater you can come back to your decisions by pressing “My decisions” in the main menu. If you choose one of decisions you will see Descartes Square again and after clicking each square you will see the list of your previous answers. You can also add answers to any square by pressing “+”.\nYou can delete all decisions by pressing “x” or edit/delete particular decision by durable press on it in “My decisions” menu. Options of deleting and editing are also present in each square in answers.</p></string>
    <string name="noDecisions">The list of decisions is empty</string>
    <string name="no_decisions_yet">No decisions yet</string>
</resources>